Richard York Gallery
Archives of American Art, Smithsonian Institution
- Artists' Artwork Files, circa 1865-2004, Series 2:; (Boxes 7-64; 56.85 linear feet)
  - General, circa 1865-2004, 2.1:
    - Torr, Helen, 3117CY: Crimson and Green Leaves, 1990-1991 (Box 59, Folder 31)
    - Torr, Helen, 3353CY: Stones and Nasturtium, 1991-1992 (Box 59, Folder 32)
    - Torr, Helen, 3660CY: Drapery Study, 1992, 1994 (Box 59, Folder 33)
    - Torr, Helen, 5030CY: Drawing for Houses on a Barge, 1996-1998 (Box 59, Folder 34)
    - Torres, Horatio, 7518RY: Nude with Blue Background, 2000 (Box 59, Folder 35)
    - Torrey, Elliott, 291CY: Crashing Wave, 1981 (Box 59, Folder 36)
    - Toulouse-Lautrec, Henri de, 7645CY: Monsieur Sescau au Moulin Rouge, 2001 (Box 59, Folder 37)
    - Toulouse-Lautrec, Henri de, 7646CY: Lady with Hat, 2001 (Box 59, Folder 38)
    - Tracy, J.M., 2542CY: Spaniel, 1988 (Box 59, Folder 39)
    - Tracy, J.M., 2565CY: Irish Setter, 1988-1989 (Box 59, Folder 40)
    - Trumbull, John (Attributed), 1706LY: Washington, circa 1986 (Box 59, Folder 41)
    - Trumbull, John, 1823CY: Study for the Death of General Warren, 1986-2000 (Box 59, Folder 42)
    - Trumbull, John, 4106CY: Study for the Death of General Warren, 1994-1995 (Box 59, Folder 43)
    - Trumbull, John, 7149CY: Portrait of John Vernet, 2000 (Box 59, Folder 44)
    - Trunk, Herman, 2194RY: Landscape With House and Trees, 1987, 1989 (Box 59, Folder 45)
    - Trunk, Herman, 2706RY: Valentine, 1989, 1998 (Box 59, Folder 46)
    - Trunk, Herman, 2793RY: Summer Landscape, 1989, 1997 (Box 59, Folder 47)
    - Trunk, Herman, 3339CY: Sailboats 7 and 8, 1979, 1991-1992 (Box 59, Folder 48)
    - Trunk, Herman, 3600CY: Porthole, 1992 (Box 59, Folder 49)
    - Tsireh, Awa, 2594CY: Green Corn Ceremony, 1988-1991 (Box 59, Folder 50)
    - Tucker, Allen, 6103CY: The Pond, 1997 (Box 59, Folder 51)
    - Turner, James [Joseph Mallord William], 1542CY: East Malling Abbey, Kent, 1985 (Box 59, Folder 52)
    - Twachtman, John Henry, 1543CY: Winter Landscape, 1985 (Box 59, Folder 53)
    - Twachtman, John Henry, 1602CY: San Miniato, Florence, 1985 (Box 59, Folder 54)
    - Twachtman, John Henry, 1633CY: Woodland Stream in Spring, 1985-1989 (Box 59, Folder 55)
    - Twachtman, John Henry, 1715RY: Landscape With House and Trees, 1986 (Box 59, Folder 56)
    - Twachtman, John Henry, 2195CY: Country Path, 1987-1988 (Box 59, Folder 57)
    - Twachtman, John Henry, 3280CY: Gray Day, 1990-1992 (Box 59, Folder 58)
    - Twachtman, John Henry, 3816CY: Gray Landscape, 1993 (Box 59, Folder 59)
    - Twachtman, John Henry, 4117CY: Harbor Scene, 1994 (Box 59, Folder 60)
    - Twachtman, John Henry, 4962CY: Country Road, 1996, 1998 (Box 59, Folder 61)
    - Twachtman, John Henry, 6129CY: Winter Scene (Fake), 1997 (Box 59, Folder 62)
    - Tyler, James Gale, 7029CY: The Home Stretch, 1999 (Box 59, Folder 63)
    - Tyler, N.R. [William R.], 6058CY: Two Boys Fishing (Duplicate File to 3426CY), 1997-1998 (Box 59, Folder 64)
    - Tyler, William R., 3426CY: Black Mountain, Lake George, 1991, 1997-1998 (Box 59, Folder 65)
    - Tyron, Dwight, 1376CY: Early Morning - Sunrise, 1984 (Box 59, Folder 66)
    - Tyron, Dwight, 4616CY: Twilight in New England, 1995 (Box 59, Folder 67)
    - Tyron, Dwight, 7023CY: Dawn: Early Spring, 1999 (Box 59, Folder 68)
    - Ufer, Walter, 3193CY: Her Treasury Jar, 1991 (Box 59, Folder 69)
    - Ulrich, Charles F., 1620CY: Young Girl Embroidering, 1985-1987 (Box 59, Folder 70)
    - Utrillo, Maurice, 1780CY: Eglise de Banlieue, 1986 (Box 59, Folder 71)
    - Vail, Eugene, 1691CY: Marine, 1986-1987 (Box 59, Folder 72)
    - Vail, Eugene, 2180CY: Dordrecht, 1987 (Box 59, Folder 73)
    - Vail, Eugene, 2214CY, 1988 (Box 59, Folder 74)
    - Vail, Eugene, 2272CY: Old Walls, Venice, 1988-1992 (Box 59, Folder 75)
    - Vail, Eugene, 2894LY: Old Walls, Venice, circa 1989 (Box 59, Folder 76)
    - Vail, Eugene, 2946CY: Old Walls, Venice, 1989-1992 (Box 59, Folder 77)
    - Van Den Hem, Pieter, 1785RY: Café Derras, Paris, 1986 (Box 59, Folder 78)
    - Van Hook Bean, Caroline, 3239CY: Little Church Around the Corner, 1991 (Box 59, Folder 79)
    - Van Os, Margaritha M., 1670JY: Still-Life with Fruit, 1986 (Box 59, Folder 80)
    - Van Schaik, Stephen Wilson, 3366CY: The Turkish Idlers, 1991 (Box 59, Folder 81)
    - Vasilieff, Nicholas, 3771CY: At the Opera, 1992-1994, 2002 (Box 59, Folder 82)
    - Vasilieff, Nicholas, 3772CY: Olympia, 1992-1994, 2002 (Box 59, Folder 83)
    - Vasilieff, Nicholas, 3773CY: Untitled Still Life, 1992-1994, 2002 (Box 59, Folder 84)
    - Vasilieff, Nicholas, 4143LY: Woman and Child, 1994, 2002 (Box 59, Folder 85)
    - Vasilieff, Nicholas, 4144LY: Gypsies, 1994, 2002 (Box 59, Folder 86)
    - Vasilieff, Nicholas, 4145LY: Tabletop Still Life, 1994, 2002 (Box 59, Folder 87)
    - Vasilieff, Nicholas, 8572CY-8583CY, 2002 (Box 59, Folder 88)
    - Vedder, Elihu, 247CY: Classical Head of a Greek Boy, 1981-1985 (Box 59, Folder 89)
    - Vedder, Elihu, 606CY: The Labyrinth, 1982 (Box 59, Folder 90)
    - Vedder, Elihu, 1531CY: The Old Mill, Bordighera, 1985, 1987 (Box 59, Folder 91)
    - Vedder, Elihu, 1555CY: Laboring in the Fields Before the Colossi of Memnon, 1985 (Box 59, Folder 92)
    - Vedder, Elihu, 1595CY: Over the Roofs at Capo le Case, Rome, 1985 (Box 59, Folder 93)
    - Vedder, Elihu, 2182CY: The Music Party, 1987-1988, 1993, 1998 (Box 59, Folder 94)
    - Vedder, Elihu, 2641CY: A Reverie, 1989, 1993-1994 (Box 59, Folder 95)
    - Vedder, Elihu, 2796LY: Windswept Olive Trees, Bordighera, 1990 (Box 59, Folder 96)
    - Vedder, Elihu, 2798LY: Poppies, 1989 (Box 59, Folder 97)
    - Vedder, Elihu, 2889LY: Off Pier-Head, Viareggio, 1989 (Box 59, Folder 98)
    - Vedder, Elihu, 2905CY: Fable of the Miller and His Son, 1989-1990 (Box 59, Folder 99)
    - Vedder, Elihu, 3983CY: Superest Invictus Amor or Love Ever Present, 1993-1997 (Box 59, Folder 100)
    - Vedder, Elihu, 4242CY: Italian Landscape Near Porto d'Anzio, 1994 (Box 59, Folder 101)
    - Vedder, Elihu, 4529CY: A Reverie, 1995 (Box 59, Folder 102)
    - Vianden, Heinrich, 1096CY: Evening, 1983-1984 (Box 60, Folder 1)
    - Vlaminck, Maurice de, 433JY: La Vallee de Nesles, 1978, 1981-1985 (Box 60, Folder 2)
    - Vollon, Alexis, 153CY: La Seine a Paris, 1981 (Box 60, Folder 3)
    - Von Wiegand, Charmion, 276CY: Geometric Abstraction, 1981 (Box 60, Folder 4)
    - Vonnoh, Bessie Potter, 2944CY: Daydreams, 1990 (Box 60, Folder 5)
    - Vonnoh, Bessie Potter, 7144CY: Young Mother, 2000 (Box 60, Folder 6)
    - Vonnoh, Robert, 1352CY: Happy Hours, 1984-1985 (Box 60, Folder 7)
    - Vries, Jacob Feyt de, 4137LY: Naval Engagement, 1994 (Box 60, Folder 8)
    - Vytlacil, Vaclav, 2551RY: Cubist Composition, 1988, 1990 (Box 60, Folder 9)
    - Wagner, Jacob, 2057JY: Simplicity, 1999-2000 (Box 60, Folder 10)
    - Wagner, Jacob, 9156CY: Lady in White Reading, 2003-2004 (Box 60, Folder 11)
    - Walker, Charles Alvah, 2649RY: Backyard, Revere, Massachusetts, 1944, 1989-1990 (Box 60, Folder 12)
    - Walker, Henry Oliver, 2731CY: Rosalind (Annie Page), 1989 (Box 60, Folder 13)
    - Walker, William Aiken, 921CY: Cabin Scene, 1983-1984 (Box 60, Folder 14)
    - Walker, William Aiken, 922CY: Cotton Picker, 1983 (Box 60, Folder 15)
    - Walker, William Aiken, 1456CY: Portrait of a Lady, 1985, 1987 (Box 60, Folder 16)
    - Walker, William Aiken, 2549CY: In the Cotton Field, 1988 (Box 60, Folder 17)
    - Walker, William Aiken, 7115CY: Man with Fish, 1999 (Box 60, Folder 18)
    - Walker, William Aiken, 7116CY: Man Holding a Possum, 1999 (Box 60, Folder 19)
    - Walkley, David B., 7111CY: Woman in a Garden, 1999, 2003 (Box 60, Folder 20)
    - Walkowitz, Abraham, 262CY: Untitled (City Abstraction), 1981-1982 (Box 60, Folder 21)
    - Walkowitz, Abraham, 3077CY: New York City #1, 1990-1994 (Box 60, Folder 22)
    - Walkowitz, Abraham, 3078CY: New York City #2, 1990-1994 (Box 60, Folder 23)
    - Walkowitz, Abraham, 3079CY: New York City #3, 1990-1994 (Box 60, Folder 24)
    - Walkowitz, Abraham, 3080CY: New York City #4, 1990-1994 (Box 60, Folder 25)
    - Walkowitz, Abraham, 3081CY: Isadora Duncan, 1990-1994 (Box 60, Folder 26)
    - Walkowitz, Abraham, 3457CY: City Abstraction (Ink), 1991 (Box 60, Folder 27)
    - Walkowitz, Abraham, 3458CY: City Abstraction (Watercolor), 1991 (Box 60, Folder 28)
    - Walkowitz, Abraham, 4588CY: Rest Day, Lake George, 1995 (Box 60, Folder 29)
    - Walkowitz, Abraham, 7066CY: Boats in Harbor, 1999 (Box 60, Folder 30)
    - Walkowitz, Abraham, 7069CY: Figures on the Porch, 1999 (Box 60, Folder 31)
    - Walkowitz, Abraham, 7070CY: Fishermen, 1999 (Box 60, Folder 32)
    - Walkowitz, Abraham, 7071CY: Floral Still Life, 1999 (Box 60, Folder 33)
    - Walkowitz, Abraham, 7072CY: Abstract Composition, 1999 (Box 60, Folder 34)
    - Walkowitz, Abraham, 7094CY: Woman Sewing, 1999 (Box 60, Folder 35)
    - Walkowitz, Abraham, 7095CY: Italian Village, 1999 (Box 60, Folder 36)
    - Walkowitz, Abraham, 7096CY: Harbor Scene, 1999 (Box 60, Folder 37)
    - Walkowitz, Abraham, 7097CY: Improvisation: Coney Island #1, 1999-2000 (Box 60, Folder 38)
    - Walkowitz, Abraham, 7098CY: Coney Island Beach Scene, 1999 (Box 60, Folder 39)
    - Walkowitz, Abraham, 7099CY: Hillside Landscape, 1999 (Box 60, Folder 40)
    - Walkowitz, Abraham, 7100CY: Circus, 1999 (Box 60, Folder 41)
    - Walkowitz, Abraham, 7101CY: Figures in a Landscape, 1999 (Box 60, Folder 42)
    - Walkowitz, Abraham, 7102CY: Seascape, 1999 (Box 60, Folder 43)
    - Walkowitz, Abraham, 7103CY: Houses in a Landscape, 1999 (Box 60, Folder 44)
    - Wall, A.S., 3337CY: (Landscape with River), 1991 (Box 60, Folder 45)
    - Wall, William Coventry, 2779CY: River Vista with Steamboat, 1989-1990, 1996 (Box 60, Folder 46)
    - Wall, William Coventry, 2780CY: River with Flatboatman, 1989-1990, 1996 (Box 60, Folder 47)
    - Wall, William [Coventry], 3338CY: Late Summer, 1991, 1993 (Box 60, Folder 48)
    - Wall, William Coventry, 3517CY: Fishermen at River with Water Lilies, 1992 (Box 60, Folder 49)
    - Wall, William Coventry, 3518CY: River Scene with Log Cabin, 1992 (Box 60, Folder 50)
    - Wall, William Guy, 3699CY: View of the Upper Hudson, 1992-1993 (Box 60, Folder 51)
    - Wall, William Guy, 4006CY: Passaic Falls, New Jersey, 1993-1994 (Box 60, Folder 52)
    - Wall, William Guy, 4018LY: Seascape with Gaff-Rigged Sailboats, 1993 (Box 60, Folder 53)
    - Wall, William Guy, 9466CY: View Near Hadley's Falls, 2003-2004 (Box 60, Folder 54)
    - Waller, Frank, 3367CY: On the Nile, 1991 (Box 60, Folder 55)
    - Walley, Abigail B., 1567CY: Toys of Childhood, 1985 (Box 60, Folder 56)
    - Walter, Martha, 606CY: Children Against the Sky, 1982 (Box 60, Folder 57)
    - Walter, Martha, 1553CY: Beach People, 1985 (Box 60, Folder 58)
    - Walter, Martha, 4156CY: Bath Beach, Massachusetts, 1994 (Box 60, Folder 59)
    - Walter, Martha, 4157CY: In the Smokies, 1994, 2003 (Box 60, Folder 60)
    - Walter, Martha, 4158CY: Promenade in the Park, 1994, 1998 (Box 60, Folder 61)
    - Walter, Martha, 4159CY: Promenade - Zara, 1994 (Box 60, Folder 62)
    - Walter, Martha, 4160CY: Venice, August; Murphy, J. Francis, 4155CY: Landscape, 1994, 2004 (Box 60, Folder 63)
    - Walter, Martha, 4161CY: Windy Day in the Garden, 1994, 1998 (Box 60, Folder 64)
    - Ward, John Quincy Adams, 7692RY: Indian Hunter Clock, 1999-2003 (Box 60, Folder 65)
    - Warner, Olin Levi, 1110CY: Twilight, 1983 (Box 60, Folder 66)
    - Warshawsky, Able George, 1730JY: Le Quai en Bretagne, 1986, 1994 (Box 60, Folder 67)
    - Warshawsky, Able George, 1805JY: Road Through a French Village, 1986 (Box 60, Folder 68)
    - Watkins, Carleton, 4957CY: Piwyac, Vernal Fall, 300 ft., Yosemite, 1996 (Box 60, Folder 69)
    - Watkins, Carleton, 4958CY: Vernal Fall and Nevada Fall From Glacier Point, Yosemite, 1996-1997 (Box 60, Folder 70)
    - Waugh, Frederick Judd, 1689CY: Surf and Spindrift, 1986, 1988 (Box 60, Folder 71)
    - Waugh, Frederick Judd, 3537CY: Full Tide, 1992 (Box 60, Folder 72)
    - Waugh, Frederick Judd, 3650RY: The Channel, 1992, 1994 (Box 60, Folder 73)
    - Waugh, Frederick Judd, 4032CY: North River No. 4, 1993-1994 (Box 60, Folder 74)
    - Waugh, Frederick Judd, 8487CY: Coastal Scene, 2002 (Box 60, Folder 75)
    - Way, Andrew John Henry, [980CY]: Still Life with Grapes, 1983 (Box 60, Folder 76)
    - Way, Andrew John Henry, 4019CY: A Bunch of Grapes, 1993 (Box 60, Folder 77)
    - Webb, A.C., 2234CY: Lac de Goube, 1988 (Box 60, Folder 78)
    - Weber, Carl, 1191CY: Southern Landscape, 1984, 1987 (Box 60, Folder 79)
    - Weber, Idelle, 1732CY: Cooper Union Trash, 1985-1986 (Box 60, Folder 80)
    - Weber, Max, 502CY: Roof Tops, 1982-1983 (Box 60, Folder 81)
    - Weber, Max, 839CY: Flowers, 1982-1983 (Box 60, Folder 82)
    - Weber, Max, 1452CY: Swimmers, 1984-1985 (Box 60, Folder 83)
    - Weber, Max, 1989CY: New York, 1987-1988 (Box 60, Folder 84)
    - Weber, Max, 2278CY: The City, 1988-1989 (Box 60, Folder 85)
    - Weber, Max, 2279CY: Pears, 1988-1989 (Box 60, Folder 86)
    - Weber, Max, 2280CY: Bathers, 1988-1989 (Box 60, Folder 87)
    - Weber, Max, 4460CY: Portrait of a Man, 1995 (Box 60, Folder 88)
    - Weber, Max, 4788CY: New York, 1996 (Box 60, Folder 89)
    - Weber, Max, 7535CY: Cubist Drawing, 2000, 2002 (Box 60, Folder 90)
    - Weber, Paul, 1496CY: Connestoga Crossing, 1985 (Box 60, Folder 91)
    - Weber, Paul, 1538CY: The Delaware Water Gap, 1985 (Box 60, Folder 92)
    - Weber, Paul, 3512CY: In the Catskills, 1992 (Box 60, Folder 93)
    - Weber, Paul, 6906CY: In the Catskills, 1999 (Box 60, Folder 94)
    - Weber, Paul, 7143JY: Summer Landscape, 1999, 2002 (Box 60, Folder 95)
    - Weber, Philipp, 3623JY: Falls of Yosemite, 1992-1993 (Box 60, Folder 96)
    - Webster, Edward Ambrose, 5014CY: Wild Grape, Bermuda, 1996 (Box 60, Folder 97)
    - Wedgwood and Co., 3992RY: Pate-sur-Pate Vase, 1993 (Box 60, Folder 98)
    - Weeks, Edwin Lord, 1789CY: The Vase Seller, 1986 (Box 60, Folder 99)
    - Weeks, Edwin Lord, 684CY: A Moorish Guard, 1982 (Box 60, Folder 100)
    - Weeks, Edwin Lord, 8496CY: Moroccan Landscape, 2002 (Box 60, Folder 101)
    - Weir, Julian Alden, 1420CY: Country Road, Near Branchville, Connecticut, 1984-1985 (Box 60, Folder 102)
    - Weir, Julian Alden, 4726CY: Peacock Feathers, 1987-1996 (Box 60, Folder 103)
    - Weir, Julian Alden, 4918CY: The Farmer's Lawn, 1996, 2000 (Box 60, Folder 104)
    - Wells, H.M., 4061LY: Hunter and Dogs, 1993 (Box 60, Folder 105)
    - Wendel, Theodore: Flowering Fields, Giverny, 1986 (Box 60, Folder 106)
    - Wendel, Theodore, 2633RY: Moonrise, Cape Ann, 1989, 1994 (Box 60, Folder 107)
    - Wendel, Theodore, 2903CY: Byways of Venice, 1989-1990 (Box 60, Folder 108)
    - Wendt, William, 1524RY: Emerald Bay, Laguna Beach, 1985 (Box 60, Folder 109)
    - Wendt, William, 4970CY: Green Fields, 1996 (Box 60, Folder 110)
    - Wengenroth, Stow, 6130CY: Port Clyde, Maine, 1997 (Box 60, Folder 111)
    - West, Benjamin, 3984CY: St. Michael, 1993-1999 (Box 60, Folder 112)
    - West, Benjamin, 4020LY: Knowledge Enlightening the World, 1993 (Box 60, Folder 113)
    - West, Benjamin, 4237CY: Alfred the Great Dividing His Loaf with a Pilgram (Study), 1994-1998 (Box 60, Folder 114)
    - West, Benjamin, 6631CY: The Choice of Hercules, 1998 (Box 60, Folder 115)
    - West, Benjamin, 6632CY: A Group of Figures by a Doorway, 1998 (Box 60, Folder 116)
    - Weston, Edward, 855CY: Green Pepper, 1982-1983 (Box 60, Folder 117)
    - Weston, Edward, 4955CY: Dunes, Oceano, 1996 (Box 60, Folder 118)
    - Weston, Edward, 4956CY: Eroded Rock, Point Lobos, 1996 (Box 60, Folder 119)
    - Weston, Harold, 4641CY: Narcissus, 1995-1996 (Box 60, Folder 120)
    - Wetherill, Elisha Kent Kane, 977CY: Daydreams, 1983 (Box 60, Folder 121)
    - Wetherill, Elisha Kent Kane, 1165CY: Morning, East Side (Fish Market), 1984 (Box 60, Folder 122)
    - Wetherill, Elisha Kent Kane, 1166CY: Delicatessen, 1984 (Box 60, Folder 123)
    - Wetherill, Elisha Kent Kane, 1806CY: Breton Farmyard, 1986 (Box 61, Folder 1)
    - Wetherill, Elisha Kent Kane, 1807CY: Ilse Aux Moines, 1986 (Box 61, Folder 2)
    - Wetherill, Elisha Kent Kane, 1808CY: Sidewalk Market, 1986, 1990-1991 (Box 61, Folder 3)
    - Wetherill, Elisha Kent Kane, 1809CY: Clearing Clouds, 1986 (Box 61, Folder 4)
    - Wetherill, Elisha Kent Kane, 1811CY: Breton Boudoir, 1986 (Box 61, Folder 5)
    - Wetherill, Elisha Kent Kane, 1812CY: Self Portrait, 1986-1987 (Box 61, Folder 6)
    - Wetherill, Elisha Kent Kane, 1813CY: Brittany Harbor, 1986, 1989 (Box 61, Folder 7)
    - Wetherill, Elisha Kent Kane, 1814CY: Port Nerahlts, 1986-1987 (Box 61, Folder 8)
    - Wetherill, Elisha Kent Kane, 1815CY: The Nurse, 1986 (Box 61, Folder 9)
    - Wetherill, Elisha Kent Kane, 1816CY: Contemplation, 1986 (Box 61, Folder 10)
    - Wetherill, Elisha Kent Kane, 1817CY: The Sisters, 1986 (Box 61, Folder 11)
    - Weyl, Max, 2791CY: New England Winter, 1989 (Box 61, Folder 12)
    - Weyl, Max, 3988CY: A Glimpse of Washington from Arlington Heights, Virginia, 1993-1996 (Box 61, Folder 13)
    - Wheeler, Steve, 6171CY: Arkansas Traveler, 1998 (Box 61, Folder 14)
    - Wheeler, Steve, 6172CY: Cowboy Standing, 1998 (Box 61, Folder 15)
    - Wheeler, Steve, 6173CY: Little Joe Picking His Nose, 1998 (Box 61, Folder 16)
    - Wheeler, Steve, 6174CY: Man Menacing Woman, 1998, 2002 (Box 61, Folder 17)
    - Wheeler, Steve, 6175CY: Portrait of Mother and Child, 1998 (Box 61, Folder 18)
    - Wheeler, Steve, 6176CY: The Jewel Thief, 1998-2000 (Box 61, Folder 19)
    - Wheeler, Steve, 6177CY: Untitled (Woman in Hat), 1998 (Box 61, Folder 20)
    - Wheeler, Steve, 6178CY: Untitled, 1998 (Box 61, Folder 21)
    - Wheeler, Steve, 6179CY: Untitled, 1998 (Box 61, Folder 22)
    - Wheeler, Steve, 6180CY: Untitled, 1998 (Box 61, Folder 23)
    - Wheeler, Steve, 6181CY: Untitled, 1998 (Box 61, Folder 24)
    - Wheeler, Steve, 6182CY: Untitled Abstraction, 1998, 2001 (Box 61, Folder 25)
    - Wheeler, Steve, 6183CY: Untitled Abstraction, 1998 (Box 61, Folder 26)
    - Wheeler, Steve, 6184CY: Wild Chase, 1998-1999 (Box 61, Folder 27)
    - Wheeler, Steve, 6185CY: Woman Eating a Hot Dog, 1998 (Box 61, Folder 28)
    - Wheeler, Steve, 6186CY: Young Man Not Afraid to Talk to His Mother-in-Law, 1998-2000 (Box 61, Folder 29)
    - Wheeler, Steve, 6187CY: A Pica of T, 1998 (Box 61, Folder 30)
    - Wheeler, Steve, 6188CY: Big Shape, 1998 (Box 61, Folder 31)
    - Wheeler, Steve, 6189CY: Big Shape (From "Hello Steve"), 1998 (Box 61, Folder 32)
    - Wheeler, Steve, 6190CY: Brooklyn in QT Formation, 1993, 1998 (Box 61, Folder 33)
    - Wheeler, Steve, 6191CY: Frontispiece, 1998, 2002 (Box 61, Folder 34)
    - Wheeler, Steve, 6192CY: Introducing Miss America, circa 1947, 1998 (Box 61, Folder 35)
    - Wheeler, Steve, 6193CY: Little Joe Picking His Nose, 1998 (Box 61, Folder 36)
    - Wheeler, Steve, 6194CY: Marine Garden, 1998 (Box 61, Folder 37)
    - Wheeler, Steve, 6195CY: Peg Taking a Drag, 1998 (Box 61, Folder 38)
    - Wheeler, Steve, 6196CY: Portrait of Essew, 1997-1998 (Box 61, Folder 39)
    - Wheeler, Steve, 6197CY: Power of Memory, 1998, 2002 (Box 61, Folder 40)
    - Wheeler, Steve, 6198CY: Prelude in Red, 1998 (Box 61, Folder 41)
    - Wheeler, Steve, 6199CY: Sheik and Private Leon, 1998 (Box 61, Folder 42)
    - Wheeler, Steve, 6200CY: Thunder and Short Beer, 1998 (Box 61, Folder 43)
    - Wheeler, Steve, 6201CY: Two Smiles, 1998 (Box 61, Folder 44)
    - Wheeler, Steve, 6202CY: Decoy for Dog, 1998 (Box 61, Folder 45)
    - Wheeler, Steve, 6203CY: Green Garden, 1998 (Box 61, Folder 46)
    - Wheeler, Steve, 6204CY: Leon Reappears, 1998, 2000 (Box 61, Folder 47)
    - Wheeler, Steve, 6205CY: The Magic Horn, 1998-1999 (Box 61, Folder 48)
    - Wheeler, Steve, 6206CY: Untitled, 1998 (Box 61, Folder 49)
    - Wheeler, Steve, 6207CY: Untitled, 1998-2003 (Box 61, Folder 50)
    - Wheeler, Steve, 6208CY: Untitled, 1998 (Box 61, Folder 51)
    - Wheeler, Steve, 6209CY: Untitled, 1998 (Box 61, Folder 52)
    - Wheeler, Steve, 6210CY: Untitled, 1998 (Box 61, Folder 53)
    - Wheeler, Steve, 6211CY: Untitled, 1998 (Box 61, Folder 54)
    - Wheeler, Steve, 6212CY: Untitled, 1998 (Box 61, Folder 55)
    - Wheeler, Steve, 6213CY: Untitled, 1998 (Box 61, Folder 56)
    - Wheeler, Steve, 6214CY: Untitled Abstraction, 1998 (Box 61, Folder 57)
    - Wheeler, Steve, 6215CY: Untitled Abstraction, 1998-1999 (Box 61, Folder 58)
    - Wheeler, Steve, 6216CY: Untitled Abstraction, 1998 (Box 61, Folder 59)
    - Wheeler, Steve, 6217CY: Vulcan, 1998-2003 (Box 61, Folder 60)
    - Wheeler, Steve, 6218CY: Self Portrait, 1998 (Box 61, Folder 61)
    - Wheeler, Steve, 6219CY: Untitled, Abstract Studies, 1998 (Box 61, Folder 62)
    - Wheeler, Steve, 6220CY: Untitled, Abstract Studies, 1998 (Box 61, Folder 63)
    - Wheeler, Steve, 6221CY: Untitled, Abstract Studies, 1998 (Box 61, Folder 64)
    - Wheeler, Steve, 6222CY: Untitled, Abstract Studies, 1998 (Box 61, Folder 65)
    - Wheeler, Steve, 6223CY: Marine Garden, 1998 (Box 61, Folder 66)
    - Wheeler, Steve, 6224CY: Portrait of Essew (Cover From "Hello Steve"), 1998 (Box 61, Folder 67)
    - Wheeler, Steve, 6225CY: Untitled Abstraction, 1998 (Box 61, Folder 68)
    - Wheeler, Steve, 6226CY: Untitled Abstraction, 1998, 2000 (Box 61, Folder 69)
    - Wheeler, Steve, 6227CY: Untitled Abstraction, 1998 (Box 61, Folder 70)
    - Wheeler, Steve, 6228CY: Introducing Miss America (Drawing From "Hello Steve"), 1998 (Box 61, Folder 71)
    - Wheeler, Steve, 6229CY: The Pica of T, 1998 (Box 61, Folder 72)
    - Wheeler, Steve, 6230CY: Untitled, Sketchbook Studies, 1998 (Box 61, Folder 73)
    - Wheeler, Steve, 6231CY: Untitled, Sketchbook Studies, 1998 (Box 61, Folder 74)
    - Wheeler, Steve, 6232CY: Untitled, Sketchbook Studies, 1998 (Box 61, Folder 75)
    - Wheeler, Steve, 6233CY: Untitled (Inside Cover From "Hello Steve"), 1998 (Box 61, Folder 76)
    - Wheeler, Steve, 6234CY: Untitled (Inside Cover From "Hello Steve"), 1998 (Box 61, Folder 77)
    - Wheeler, Steve, 6235CY: Untitled (From "Hello Steve"), 1998-1999 (Box 61, Folder 78)
    - Wheeler, Steve, 6236CY: Girl Whistling, 1998 (Box 61, Folder 79)
    - Wheeler, Steve, 6237CY: Moth, 1998 (Box 61, Folder 80)
    - Wheeler, Steve, 6238CY: Untitled, 1998-1999 (Box 61, Folder 81)
    - Wheeler, Steve, 6248CY: The Clarinet Player, 1998-2001 (Box 61, Folder 82)
    - Wheeler, Steve, 6340CY: Humpty Dumpty, 1998 (Box 61, Folder 83)
    - Wheeler, Steve, 6356LY: Alladin Guiding Caprin, 1998 (Box 61, Folder 84)
    - Wheeler, Steve, 6416LY: Mother-in-Law, 1998 (Box 61, Folder 85)
    - Wheeler, Steve, 6582CY: Two Smiles, 1998 (Box 61, Folder 86)
    - Wheeler, Steve, 6583CY: Sheik and Private Leon, 1998 (Box 61, Folder 87)
    - Wheeler, Steve, 6584CY: Big Shape, 1998 (Box 61, Folder 88)
    - Wheeler, Steve, 6585CY: Peg Taking a Drag, 1998 (Box 61, Folder 89)
    - Wheeler, Steve, 6586CY: A Pica of T, 1998 (Box 61, Folder 90)
    - Wheeler, Steve, 6587CY: Marine Garden, 1998 (Box 61, Folder 91)
    - Wheeler, Steve, 6588CY: Nick Carter, 1998 (Box 61, Folder 92)
    - Wheeler, Steve, 6589CY: The Power of Memory, 1998 (Box 61, Folder 93)
    - Wheeler, Steve, 6590CY: Little Joe Picking His Nose, 1998 (Box 61, Folder 94)
    - Wheeler, Steve, 6591CY: Prelude in Red, 1998 (Box 61, Folder 95)
    - Wheeler, Steve, 6592CY: Thunder and Short Beer, 1998 (Box 61, Folder 96)
    - Wheeler, Steve, 6593CY: Brooklyn in QT Formation, 1998 (Box 61, Folder 97)
    - Wheeler, Steve, 6594CY: Introducing Miss America, 1998 (Box 61, Folder 98)
    - Wheeler, Steve, 6598CY: Nick Carter at Work, 1998 (Box 61, Folder 99)
    - Wheeler, Steve, 6654CY: A Pica of T, 1998 (Box 61, Folder 100)
    - Wheeler, Steve, 6855aCY: Hello Steve, 1998 (Box 61, Folder 101)
    - Wheeler, Steve, 6855bCY: Hello Steve, 1998 (Box 61, Folder 102)